In this scene, we will explore some
fascinating generalizations of the Mandelbrot Set.
These include the Multibrot Sets, the
Tricorn, and the 4D Mandelbrot Set.
First, let's look at the Multibrot Sets.
The Multibrot Sets are a generalization of the
Mandelbrot Set, where the exponent in the iteration
formula is replaced with a diffrent degree.
Observe how the fractal changes as we vary the exponent.
Next, we explore the Tricorn sets.
The Tricorn is generated using the iteration formula where the complex conjugate of
z is squared and added to c, instead of just z squared.
Let's observe the changes as we vary the exponent here as well.